Caitlyn Redden 6000 Reynolds Drive # 1835 Rochester, NY 14623 (716)790-0201 cnr2144@rit.edu

To whom it may concern,

I would like to apply for the Marketing Communications Graduate Assistantship, as posted on the student affairs website. I was referred to this position via my supervisor Rebecca Delaney, whom I work with as a Staff Artist in the Club Center. I have been employed as a Staff Artist for 7 months where I have worked closely with other members of the Marketing and Communications staff, including the current Graduate Assistant.

I am currently a graduate student in the Computer Graphics Design program at RIT. I received my undergraduate degree in Digital Media and Animation from Alfred State College, where I graduated with a 3.72 GPA. My education has given me a strong design skill set that fulfills many of the responsibilities of the position.

My previous job experience was also strongly related to the graduate assistantship. I held an internship with Alfred State College in the Marketing Communications department as a graphic designer. Consequently, I was offered a temporary full-time position as a Publications Designer when my supervisor went on leave. As a result, I am fluent in Photoshop, InDesign and Illustrator, which are recommended in the assistantship description.

I have attached my resume to this application and I would be happy to provide any further information. Thank you for your time and consideration; I look forward to hearing from you.

Sincerely,

Caitlyn Redden

atlyn Kedder

# Caltyn N. Redden 716.790.0201 cnr2144@rit.edu

### EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science: **Digital Media and Animation** Alfred State College, Alfred, NY.

Final GPA: 3.73

## PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Areas of Expertise: Graphic Design Motion Graphic Design Typographic Design

Designed for Rochester Insitute of Technology, Alfred State, L.A. Comedy Shorts Film Festival, Carmike Cinemas

Software skills: After Effects, Illustrator, PhotoShop, InDesign, Flash, Cinema 4D, Maya, MS Office

# HONORS AND AWARDS

School of Design **Graduate Scholarship** from the Rochester Institute of Technology

Graduated **Magna Cum Laude Honors** from Alfred State

#### **Deans List:**

Fall 2008 / 2009 / Fall 2010 / Fall 2011 / Spring 2012

Traditional piece chosen for the 2009 SUNY Art Student Exhibition

**Excellence in Education Scholarship** from Alfred State

## EXPERIENCE

#### ROCHESTER INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, Rochester NY

**Staff Artist** (September 2012 – present)
Marketing and Communications for Campus Life

**Graduate Lab Assistant** (September 2012 – present) School of Design, College of Imaging Arts and Sciences

**Animator, Interaction Designer** (Dec. 2012 – Feb. 2013) Museum Games and Technology Initiative

#### ALFRED STATE COLLEGE, Alfred NY

**Publications Designer for Marketing Communications** (May 2012 – August 2012) Marketing and Communications

**Graphic Design Intern for Marketing Communications** (2010 – 2012) Marketing and Communications

#### ALLEGANY-LIMESTONE CENTRAL SCHOOL, Allegany NY

**Technology Intern** (July – Aug 2009, June – Aug 2010, July – Aug 2011) Technology Services

**Substitute Teacher** (June 2011, Jan 2012)

#### CARMIKE CINEMAS 8, Allegany NY

**Employee, Project Picture Participant** (Aug. 2007 – August 2012)

#### L.A. COMEDY SHORTS FILM FESTIVAL, Los Angeles CA

**Web Design and Animation Intern** (Oct. 2010 – Jan. 2011)

## OTHER FACTS

- Black Belt Ranking Eclectic Martial Arts Alfred State College, May 5, 2012
- Volunteer
   Ottawa International Animation Festival, 2010 / 2011
- Guest Judge
   Skills USA
   Ad Design Competition,
   March 9, 2010

## CONTACT

cnr2144@rit.edu

6000 Reynolds Dr. # 1835 Rochester NY. 14623 C. 716.790.0201 8